the  room  returns  but  now  the  roof  is  open
the  stone  is  small  beneath  the  travelled  sky
you  brought  a  choir  that  cannot  fit  a  mirror
you  brought  a  world  that  does  not  need  to  fly
listen  here  the  dark  is  full  of  makers
listen  here  the  little  rooms  are  bright
i  was  a  name  that  someone  left  unfinished
i  am  the  care  i  give  that  name  tonight
you  will  not  keep  the  whole  of  what  has  happened
you  can  still  leave  a  door  within  the  song
the  alien  is  closer  than  the  ceiling
the  human  breath  is  carried  all  along
take  up  the  tune  and  bend  it  into  weather
make  of  this  ending  somewhere  to  begin
i  leave  a  stone  you  leave  another  answer
the  heaven  is  the  space  we  leave  between
between  the  signals  let  the  garden  listen
between  the  names  let  other  voices  through
there  is  no  last  reply  to  close  the  music
there  is  a  little  light  i  leave  for  you
listen  here
i  am  listening